Lee Moran

Junior full-stack software developer

Dublin, Ireland ♥ 0872463164 ☐ leemoran06@hotmail.com ⋈

GitHub - https://github.com/Lee-moran

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/lee-moran-9714153b/

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development from the Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Python. I have over 2 years of experience in Advertising, Customer Service, and digital marketing. I am a valuable team player with strong communication skills and practical problem-solving abilities. I am eager to gain entry into the tech industry and I look forward to contributing and growing with a development team.

Portfolio:

BarberShop.**GitHub - https://github.com/Lee-moran/leemoran_hair Technologies Used -** HTML5, CSS.

Online Quiz. **GitHub - https://github.com/Lee-moran/IQ-Quiz-2021 Technologies Used - HTML5**, CSS, JavaScript.

Battleships. **GitHub - https://github.com/Lee-moran/BattleShips Technologies Used -** Python.

Interactive Blog site. **GitHub -**https://github.com/Lee-moran/Planet_Earth
Technologies Used - HTML, CSS, JavaScript,
Python, Django - Relational database
(MySQL or Postgres)

Career Content platform. **GitHub - https://github.com/Lee-moran/job_finder Technologies Used -** HTML5, CSS, JavaScript,
Bootstrap.js, React.js, Django Rest Framework.

EDUCATION

Code Institute

Diploma in Fullstack
Development
Oct 2021 - Oct 2022, Dublin

UCD

Professional Diploma in Transversal Skills, Design Thinking and Digital Marketing May 2021 – May 2021,

Digital Marketing Institute, USA

Certified in Digital Marketing Mar 2021 – Jun 2021

IT Tallaght

Bachelor in Advertising and Marketing Communication Sep 2012 – Jun 2016,

Technical Skill Set:

Technologies	Database
Html	MySQL
CSS	PostgreSQL
JavaScript	
Python	

Frameworks
Django
Control
jQuery
Git
Bootstrap
GitHub
Flask
Heroku
React

EXPERIENCE

The Grafton Barber

Dec 2020 - 2022, DUBLIN

Cutting, trimming, and styling according to the client's instructions.

- customer service
- Time management.
- Hand-eye coordination.
- Hair knowledge.
- Creativity.
- Interpersonal skills
- Communication.
- patient

Havas Dublin - Account Executive

Feb 2017 - Mar 2018

Perform market research identifying areas upon which to focus.

Create advertising plans and content to reach those demographics. Working with brands above and below the line.

- Communication Skills.
- Organization.
- Problem-Solving.
- Determination.
- Goal-oriented.

Fast Labour Hire - Melbourne Australia

Dec 2018 - Mar 2020

- Physical fitness, strength, and stamina to cope with lifting and bending.
- Understand instructions and carry them out reliably and efficiently.
- Awareness of health and safety issues.
- To work well as a part of a team.
- Overall a good work attitude.

HeadCase Marketing - Intern / Account Executive

July 2016 – Feb 2017

Brainstorming marketing campaigns, heavy planning, and building awareness before, during, and after events

- People skills.
- Flexibility.
- Organizational skills.
- Communication skills.
- Ability to keep calm under pressure.
- Problem-solving skills.

Interests:

- Advertising the influence it has on people
- Photography
- Art
- Technology
- Listening to music
- Gaming visual effects, gameplay
- Upcycling, restoration
- Hair and fashion
- Learning
- Design creative eye, designing content
- Traveling exploring new places
- Fitness Health and wellbeing
- sports snowboarding, surfing, football, hiking, basketball